This little place is absolutely quién rooted.
It's not like the people in the park.
It's like a keyboard.
So this is why this is a big especial board that has to be stretched.
But...
I'd like to combine Pomelo, festivals and IOUs.
On the beach!
Good morning.
Good morning, and welcome to today's program.
Today's project is
I always enjoy the delicious food
Ki-ya's
canned food.
Let's actually take it and
Let's make it!
Yay!
Today
It's so early in the morning.
I was forced to come to the beach
I'm so happy to be here.
I found myself in the rain...
This is the season
It's the summer season.
summer season.
to take
shelling ourselves.
visiting the tree house.
We
thought up
We decided to make a canned food menu
We were going to make canned food.
But we can't do it alone.
It's just the two of us.
We can't go out and get the canned goods.
We have a guest for you today.
Thank you for your hard work.
This is Mr. Akumi, a fisherman from Begistan.
Pleased to meet you.
Thank you.
It's cold.
Nice to meet you.
How long have you been a fisherman?
About 15 years.
That's great.
You're a pro.
I'm not done yet.
With such a healthy Akumi
My favorite!
Yay!
Thank you for watching!
It's coming!
That's great!
The ship has sailed.
Oh, wow.
I'm getting a little excited.
What do I do with this look?
Oh, my God!
You're so beautiful!
So beautiful!
Amazing!
Good job, guys!
We're going by air, right?
Today.
I'm up at 3:00.
2:30.
It's so bright.
I did a great video.
Sub Cat.
Thanks for watching.
Here we are, Mr. Ohkun.
Here we are, Mr. Okun.
I'm on a full ride with zero knowledge.
Let's ask him. Later.
This is where the persimmon fishery is.
The one hanging there.
Each one of those will be a persimmon.
Ehh~! That's amazing!
And now we're going to use this machine
I'm going to chop them up.
At first, the persimmons are raised in this machine.
In this kettle, the persimmons come in.
And then we pull it up.
You don't have to hold it.
Yes, I got it!
I got it!
You're worried about me.
They're worried about you.
I'll get the machine to do it.
Let's get this out of here.
I was just wondering if you'd like to...
Phone call. Phone call. That's what I'm talking about.
I thought you were going to send it.
I'm wearing this. I don't think I'll look so good in it.
Get in!
Put the Greek soup.
Siroxos.
Grated garlic.
Chili powder.Chili powder.
Sesame oil.
Salt.
Chopped garlic.
Pepper powder.
Sesame oil.
Mix well.
It's done.
Thank you for watching.
It's fresh and new!
Freshly fluffed!
That's great!
That's great.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Awesome.
I think I'm going to finish this now.
If that's it... if that's it... if that's it... if that's it...
Here, uh, just, uh... just do a quick tap here, please.
Yes!
Yay, work!
No!
I'm off!
Okay, I'll let you watch the helpers.
Come on!
Is this it?
No, over there.
Wow!
Keeper!
Yeah!
Parents' baby. Parents' baby.
Oh, my gosh!
We're going back.
Which way do we go back?
Let's go back.
My sister, she, uh...
I cut the cord that was removed.
It was a very hard job. It looks like a lot of work.
I got a lot of keys in the basket.
I knew it!
We did it!
Amazing. Abstract
Amazing.
Parking?
Parked?
Parked boat. Cute.
Here we are.
I got it!
That's great! We got so many!
This basket is full of main and it's amazing!
I got a lot of keys, each one big!
Wow! It's really great!
After this, I'd like to start peeling these keys.
You've never done this before, have you?
No!
It's the first time for both of us, so we'll give it our best shot!
Okay, now that you've prepared the persimmons
I'd like to start peeling them now.
Yay!
And now that Okae-sama is here, he will teach us how to peel the persimmons.
Yes, thank you very much.
Okay, let's do it.
First of all, I'll put this one in the front, the thin one.
Hold it firmly with your left hand.
Then I insert the blade toward the bottom of the scallop and move it 2 or 3 times.
Then, cut the scallop off, and open it like this.
Can you do it?
It's hard. It's hard.
Now, with the scallop still in this position, put this down. Put this down, put it down, put it down.
That's right.
And now it's like the scallop on the blade has been cut.
And then open it up like this.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
Now open it up.
How is it? Is it open?
That's beautiful.
Okay, now put it in my palm.
Very good.
And here, you see this scallop here?
Cut this off from the shell.
Watch your left hand.
It's hard.
How hard? It's that time with the cat.
Now, cut it off here.
Cut it tight.
That's right.
From the end.
Oh!
Wow!Oh, my gosh!
A little something extra.
Here you go.
That's great!
Very good, very good.
And let's try it again.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Good, good, good!
And pop.
Yes, OK.
Oh, it's good!
I got it!
You did pretty well!
All of these can be removed.
You can get them, if you cut them.
Yes, yes, good luck!
There you go.
Wow!
There you go. There's a toilet right there.
Yes! That's hard!
Yes!
What do you think?
Grandpa, can I eat this now?
You can eat it!
Yay! Yes!
May I? I want some!
Okay, let's get started.
Yeah! Yes! I'm so happy!
I got a peeled persimmon!
Yay! I'm so happy!
Yay!
I'm going to eat it! Bon appétit!
I'll take it!
It's huge!
It's big!
It's so big!
Bon appétit!
Mmm!
Delicious!
Hot!
That's not right.
Big
It's big.
It's getting salty!
of seawater
I didn't put anything on it
Delicious
Big and tasty
Delightful
We had a luxurious oyster
Thank you mother
Mmmmmm
Thank you for watching
Thank you for watching today. Have a nice day!
[See you soon.
There's a crab!
It's kind of alive!
Oh, my gosh!
There he is.
Crab!
It's moving!
I'm done peeling!
I just had them clean the peeled ones.
It's about 5 kilos!
5 kg!
It's heavy!
Heavy?
So heavy!
I peeled so many!
It was a lot of fun.
I was having so much fun that I had to push myself to do it!
I got so many oysters!
After this, I want to take these oysters to the oyster shop!
Yay!
We've arrived at Kimeya-san!
So I would like to give these persimmons to Tomo-san for canning!
Yes!
GO!
Hello!
Yes, welcome!
I brought some persimmons.
They're great!
I'd like to can them.
Yes, of course.
Is your friend here?
Right there.
I'll call him.
Yes, please.
Yes, hello.
I'll call Mr. Nakajima.
Okay, then.
Nakajima-san.
Yes, I'm fine.
Thank you very much.
Good morning.Good morning.
I brought these persimmons and I was wondering if you could recommend them.
Of course.
Really? Please.
I heard there were 100.
Yes.
It's definitely not 100.
There are 5 kilos.
Five kilos? That's a lot.
I think it's more than that.
I'll take it.
Yes, I'll take it.
100 pieces.
Well, then, I'd like you to go inside the factory and actually make them.
We'd like to use the machines that go inside the factory.
Please.
Yes, please.
Let's go!
Juice-Juice.
I'm looking for a machine that goes into a factory.
It might be the first time. Maybe it's not.
I like elementary school Daruki.
Is it okay?
I'm off.
Wow!
Mashima-mama!
Amazing!
There you go!
It's cold.
Looks like a fun attraction.
I cleaned you up.
All over.
Take a look inside the factory
Inside the factory
I haven't done something like this
I haven't been able to do this since elementary school.
I'm excited.
Courtesy.
I'm just trying to keep it clean.
Thank you for watching.
Yes, this is Momma.
Yes, ma'am.
My nickname in the company is Mon-chan.
Mon-chan.
C'mon.
This is Mon-chan.
I'm Kime-no-Mon-chan.
Please, please...
Please, please.
Here you go.
Please wish me a happy birthday before you finish it.
Oh, please.
Okay, I'll put it in.
Yes, I'll put it in.
Mon-chan, Mon-chan.
That's great.
You're so cute.
It's so cute. Your eyes are so big.
We complimented each other at the factory.
You can tell by the big mask that she's got a small face.
Yay! The factory is the best!
Factory magic.
Let's make it.
Oh, wow!
That's amazing!
It's like a sterilized cafe.
And shrimp, oden, right?
Shrimp are fried!
Please look at each one individually, as there may be shell skins or something like that on them.
There may also be some flakes on them, so please check them one by one.
I hope you can do that.
Please do so.
That's important.
There is a lot of steady work to be done today, so we'll do it all at once.
Oh, it's true.
If you touch it, you'll understand. It's hard to take.
It's true. It's hard work when you see it.
It's only important for one day.
It's done.
I did a quick clean-up, checked for shells, and...
It went without a hitch.
This time, there are three kinds.
We're going to sterilize them together.
I need to put a mark on them.
Otherwise, it will be hard to tell the difference later.
so I'd like to mark them first.
So I'd like to mark them first.
OK.
That's quick.
I've got a lot of stuff in there.
It's going to be a lot of work.
Yes, sir.
Is it good?
Is it thick?
It's the original can.
It's your choice.
Of course.
Is it good?Is it good?
Is it too thick?
No. Is it dense?
Thanks for watching. Have a nice day!
Subtitles online by pepper pralisi recht
Welcome back.
Welcome home
It's done.
It's ready. It's cold.
The recipe we just came up with for kanzume has arrived.
Yay! I'd like to eat it right away, but...
But I heard they have to test the kanzume for about two weeks.
I can't eat it now, so I'll have it delivered to my office later.
I'm looking forward to tasting it at the office.
Bye bye.
Oh, my God!
So, these two are the canned goods we came up with.
These two are the canned goods we came up with.
Finally!
I'm so excited!
We've been waiting two weeks.
Okay, let's open them.
Oh, that's nice.
Ta-da!
Oh!
You mixed the grated ponzu and the other stuff, right?
I did.
Tasted it, it's a little strong.
Also, I put some yuzu in it.
I put the peel of the yuzu.
I put the peel.
It smells like yuzu.
It's like this.
Next, I'd like to open it.
Please do.
Poof!
What's that? I can't tell from the looks of it.
Not at all. Oh, but it smells so good.
Ta-da! This way!
But there's, like, no shrimp or anything...
It has shrimp and mushrooms and garlic and stuff!
It looks so delicious!
Let's try it then!
Bon appétit!
Is this what you call it?
Wow! Maybe it is.
Wow! Bon appétit.
Yeah! Yeah!
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Ooh! Oh, my gosh!
Refreshing!
How's the seasoning?
Perfectly seasoned!
Not too strong, I'm glad I went with the powder flavor!
Oh! It's great!
So refreshing and delicious!
Goooood! Goooood!
I'll have some too!
Yes!
Bon appétit!
Mmm!
Yum!
Delicious?
Yeah, it's so, so, so...
It's soaked up all the olives. It's so good.
Oh, my God!
It tastes like seafood.
Really?
Yeah, it's delicious!
Want to trade?
Let's trade!
Then it's swap time!
Exchange time!
Yeah!
Bon appétit!
Mmm!
Yum!
Delicious!
Refreshing!
It's so good!
Delicious!
Not too much flavor.
Just right!
It's good, isn't it?
It's just right, isn't it?
So it arrived.
I tried the persimmon we came up with!
We tried it!
This time, we helped a little with the picking
and mixing it up, and then we tried it!
I tried it!
It was so delicious!
Thank you very much!
See you again!
Bye bye!
Subscribe to our channel
Subscribe to our channelSubscribe to our channel